Titian Ramsay Peale Sketches 1817-1875 Mss.B.P31.15d
American Philosophical Society
- Titian Ramsay Peale Sketches, 1817-1875
  - Sheep, Bighorn, n.d.; 506; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Sheep, Bighorn, n.d.; 507; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Sheep, Bighorn, n.d.; 508; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Sheep, Bighorn, n.d.; 509; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Sheep, Bighorn, n.d.; 510a; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Sheep, Bighorn, n.d.; 510b; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Sheep, Bighorn, n.d.; 511; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Sheep, Bighorn, n.d.; 512; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Skunks, n.d.; 513; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Weasels, n.d.; 514; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Wolf (female)..."Near 3 years old, Indiana", 515; Watercolor (Box 5)
  - Wolf ? (anatomical sketch), n.d.; 516; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Wolves, n.d.; 517; Ink & wash (Box 5)
  - Boulder & trees, n.d.; 518; Watercolor, pencil (Box 5)
  - Boulder & plants, n.d.; 519; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Castle, n.d.; 520; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Houses, n.d.; 521a; Pencil (Box 5)
  - House, n.d.; 521b; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Houses, n.d.; 522; Pencil (Box 5)
  - House, n.d.; 523a; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Castle, n.d.; 523b; Pencil (Box 5)
  - House & gate, n.d.; 524; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Houses, n.d.; 525; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Monogram letters: A.M.O., n.d.; 526; Pencil (Box 5)
    [Sketch: Artillery, Magpie and ?]
  - Ocean view, n.d.; 527; Pencil (Box 5)
  - T.R.P. monogram, n.d.; 528; Ink & wash (Box 5)
  - Sketch of title page, "Contribution to American Natr.", n.d.; 529; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Tree, n.d.; 530; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Wagon & horse, n.d.; 531; Pencil (Box 5)
  - Unknown figure, n.d.; 532; Ink and wash (Box 5)
  - Photocopies of Five Sketchbooks, n.d.; 533; Photocopies (Box 5)
    [Original located at Library of Congress.]